Ezz Elden Mohamed

Full Stack Web Developer

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | <u>01002368023</u> | ezzelden4work@gmail.com <u>My WebSite</u>, <u>linkedin</u> , <u>codepen</u> , <u>GitHub</u> , <u>Youtube</u>

Summary

I'm a front-end web developer. I have 5 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work, you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

Education

I'm a student in the Delta Academy, I study at the faculty of Management Information Systems. (Final year)

Skills

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | Sass | React.js | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | Php | WordPress

Professional Experience

Atheltree

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Survey
- Round Base

Web Instructor: 2021

I was giving some web development courses in my college by assembling groups of students and starting how to develop the website professionally.

Graduation projects Assistant:

2021

I was assisting students in their graduation projects, supervising them in the design and development stages, and discussing them in front of a specialized committee of doctors in the fields of technology.

Some of Project:

- Elfahd Elevetor
- Smart Parking
- Elkepash

The Lean

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Store Demo
- Youssef Allam Group
- Khozam

Afro Arab Digital

Feb 2020 - July 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Afro Arab Digital
- Bakkahlean

Devolum

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

Some of Project:

- Alemnishokran
- <u>Midstr</u>
- Islah
- Oral

Projects

Vuesax Dashboard

gitHub Live View

- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

Round Base <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React
- Company Review

See More Projects.....

Langues

Arabic : Native | English : Good Write and Speak